Dılo sürücü



berxudar@gmail.com

•

+1(929) 714 7201



linkedin.com/in/abdulkadir-sürücü

Summary

Stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/5582655/dilo-sürücü

Github: https://github.com/diloabininyeri

Youtube: https://www.youtube.com/c/dilosürücü

I have been working as a software developer for 12 years actively(this year 2022), I am originally a physics graduate, I worked as a full-stack frontend and backend developer in most projects, I have mostly written PHP for the last 6-7 years. Big data and artificial intelligence always attract my attention. I have been working on these two issues frequently lately, When the team could not find a developer to code a language they needed, I took this responsibility many times and fulfilled it, yes I am a PHP developer, but I don't just write PHP. I write in languages such as golang, python, javascript bash, etc, I have worked in many different positions for years, as a developer, as a server administrator, as a team leader, etc. software is not just about writing code software is a data structure

Experience



🔛 Software Engineer

Doping Hafıza

Sep 2020 - Sep 2021 (1 year 1 month)

An application that received millions of monthly visitors was also a company that wanted professionalism such as video streaming.

image recognition processes, Linux systems, performance, code review

- Elasticsearch
- Aws(amazon web service)
- logstash
- kibana
- MySQL
- MariaDB(master-slave cluster)
- Linux (centos-ubuntu)
- Redis(cache-master-slave-sentinel)
- Rabitmg
- core PHP
- Laravel
- Queue
- network
- nodejs
- socket
- -server

Senior PHP Developer

mpsmobile GmbH

Aug 2021 - Present (10 months +)

b2b software and eCommerce, refactoring, custom framework, etc...

- Elasticsearch
- Logstash
- Kibana
- -Redis
- -Linux
- -MySQL
- -software architectural
- -Agile (Jira)
- Flutter (mobile developer)
- Docker
- kubernetes

PHP Developer

KolayBi'

Oct 2018 - May 2019 (8 months)

Turkey of accounting systems

- php
- -laravel
- mysql
- rabitmq
- aws (amazon web service)
- angular.js

backend

sorsware

May 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 1 month)

the social media site software, customer support platform

- Laravel
- Php
- MySQL
- javascript
- CSS
- Linux

Webmaster

freelance

2010 - Present (12 years 5 months +)

software support and application development

- Docker
- Linux
- PHP (Symfony-laravel)
- Mysql
- Redis
- Elasticsearch

- Redis
- oop
- Distributed systems
- server (deploy-backup-performance) etc...
- aws(amazon web service)

Software Engineer

Balista software and Education

Jul 2016 - Jul 2017 (1 year 1 month)

map development software, An engineering application was written, a map application was written for mapping engineers,

- Symfony
- python
- node.js
- Angular.js
- leaflet.js
- Docker

N Senior PHP Developer

Nacar Design

Feb 2018 - Sep 2018 (8 months)

software and system architect e-commerce system

- Laravel
- Symfony
- Mysql
- Elasticsearch
- Redis
- Vue.js
- Redis

Senior PHP Developer

Istanbul Bilisim

Mar 2020 - Aug 2020 (6 months)

Turkey's largest e-commerce site had 30 million monthly visitors,

I was responsible for all of the below

- Database
- software
- deploy

Senior PHP Developer

PortalGrup

Apr 2016 - Apr 2017 (1 year 1 month)

Rewriting and developing software written according to the very old system according to today's world

- Cms
- Php

- mysql

Full Stack Engineer

yener akademi

Jan 2012 - Jan 2015 (3 years 1 month)

Responsible for all software processes and management, as well as writing systems, I was work as a game developer

- nodejs
- angular.js
- php
- mysql
- mongodb
- socket
- games

Software Engineer

Maysa agriculture (samsun/Turkey)

Jan 2008 - Jan 2012 (4 years 1 month)

agriculture and pharmaceutical production

Graphics software, I was responsible for all software stuff.

- wordpress
- delphi
- html-js-css
- photoshop

Education



🤊 19 mayıs üniversitesi - Samsun/Turkey

faculty of physics, graduate

2008 - 2012

I graduated from a university that provides higher mathematics and physics as well as computer education.

🚺 Ondokuz Mayıs Üniversitesi

3, Physics

2008 - 2012

Skills

php • css • jquery • angular.js • javascript • html • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • MySQL • Symfony • Laravel